Okay if you, as you've watched these segments, you'll see that tennis is a very athletic game and I want you to think about if I'm hitting a forehand like this, well one of the great poses in martial arts or in yoga is a pose like this.
So this is very good for you to do.
So you'll hold this pose, it's going to strengthen your legs and it's going to do so without any risk of injury because you're not moving any weights, you're not on a hard surface.
So, you just hold this pose; ideally hold it for a minute or longer and that means you're going to be pretty strong in the mid section and in the upper legs and you'll have good endurance and then just go to other side.
So just think of your backhand now.
So, in martial arts or in yoga, they call this a warrior pose.
So, you can see, I'm getting and I'm hitting the ball and you end up like this.
So, you have to be strong in the legs and in this part of the legs.
So, you hold this pose and you'll be amazed once again how much better your balance gets.
A lot of people because they're not strong, when they're going for a ball, they're balance is bad; they're weak.
So, I want you to think about holding some poses and developing that type of fitness because tennis is a very, very; it demands a lot out of you and you've got to put a lot into it.